

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **Details**





in www.linkedin.com/in/yee-shim-chai-s10p1

https://rachelchai0710.github.io/RacPort/

NATIONALITY

Malaysian

## **Programming Skills**

JAVA

Angular

Groovy

C-family Programming

HTML/CSS

Python

SQL

Visual Basic

Kotlin

Solidity

#### **Soft Skills**

- Fast Leaner
- Able to work under pressure
- Effective time management
- Collaboration & teamwork

#### Languages

Mandarin

English

Cantonese

Bahasa Malaysia

### **Profile**

Experienced software engineer with a strong background in financial technology. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Possesses a skill set focused on Java and Angular development. Over the past two years, I have been responsible for customizing software and ensuring the delivery of high-quality products to clients. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

# **Employment History**

## Software Engineer at Theta Service Partner Sdn Bhd

AUGUST 2022 — PRESENT

- Involved in CR development and supporting Hong Kong DBS & Charles Schwab Bank Loan Origination System.
- Developed REST APIs and integrated REST APIs.
- · Handled loan letters auto generation development.

# Software Engineer Intern at Theta Service Partner Sdn Bhd

JANUARY 2022 — JUNE 2022

- Involved in R&D for the base product.
- Supported workflow based Loan Origination System for multiple banks.
- Debugged software, identified root causes, and proposed solutions to software issues

# Quality Assurance Analyst (Internship) at Finexus SDN. BHD., Kuala Lumpur

FEBRUARY 2020 — APRIL 2020

 Assured that system meet the established standards set by the company and free from errors.

# **Educational Background**

Bachelor of Information Technology (Honours) in Software Systems Development, Tunku Abdul Rahman University of Management and Technology, Kuala Lumpur

JUNE 2020 — JULY 2022

#### Achievement:

- President's List (Jan 2021 & May 2020)
- Dean's List (Sep 2020)

CGPA: 3.91

Diploma in Science (Computer Science and Management Mathematics), Tunku Abdul Rahman University of Management and Technology, Kuala Lumpur

MAY 2018 — JUNE 2020

CGPA: 3.89

## **Projects**

#### Garageku

Developed an e-commerce car workshop mobile application for a newly established company that act as an intermediary between car workshop owners and vehicle owners.